<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to my page! on Saitejas Mopuri</title>
    <link>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to my page! on Saitejas Mopuri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter disaster detector</title>
      <link>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>github url
webapp
Twitter_real_or_not How to detect disasters using twitter tweets?
Table of contents   Define Problem
 How to detect disasters using twitter tweets?    Discover Data
 Exploratory Data Analysis(EDA) Data Visualization    Develop solutions
 Establish a baseline NLP Models LSTM Glove LSTM Bert    Deploy solution
 Automate the pipeline Deploy the solution to gcloud and firebase    Defining The Problem How can we identify the disasters through tweets?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tensorflow Developer</title>
      <link>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/certs/cert_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 11:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/certs/cert_2/</guid>
      <description>certificate
What skills are coverd in this exam?   Build and train neural network models using TensorFlow 2.x
 Build, compile and train machinelearning(ML) models using TensorFlow. Preprocess data to get it ready for use in a model. Use models to predict results. Use pre trained models (transfer learning) Build sequential models with multiplelayers. Build and train models for binaryclassification. Build and train models for multi-classcategorization Identify strategies to prevent overfitting, including augmentation and dropout    Image classification</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Practicioner</title>
      <link>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/certs/cert_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/certs/cert_1/</guid>
      <description>Digital badge
What is this certification? The AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner examination is intended for individuals who have the knowledge and skills necessary to effectively demonstrate an overall understanding of the AWS Cloud, independent of specific technical roles addressed by other AWS Certifications
Abilities Validated by the Certification   Define what the AWS Cloud is and the basic global infrastructure
  Describe basic AWS Cloud architectural principles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coursera Tensorflow in practice</title>
      <link>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/certs/cert_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/certs/cert_4/</guid>
      <description>certificate
What is this course?   In this hands-on, four-course Professional Certificate program, I have learned the necessary tools to build scalable AI-powered applications with TensorFlow
  TensorFlow is one of the most in-demand and popular open-source deep learning frameworks available today. The DeepLearning.AI TensorFlow Developer Professional Certificate program has taught me how to apply machine learning skills with TensorFlow so I can build and train powerful models</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devanagari language recognizer</title>
      <link>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>github url
webapp
Devanagari Recognizer Objective: To accuratley classify the Devanagari Characters
Table of contents  Define Problem  Can we accuratley classify the Devanagari Characters?   Discover Data  Data Visualization   Develop solutions  Machine Learning Models Hyperparameter tuning   Deploy solution  Flask and Heroku    Defining the problem What is Devanagari language?   The Nāgarī or Devanāgarī alphabet developed from eastern variants of the Gupta script called Nāgarī, which first emerged during the 8th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loan Predictions</title>
      <link>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>github url
lendingCompany Objective: Can we predict trustworthiness?
Table of contents   Define Problem
 Can we predict the right loan applicant from their background? Goals    Discover Data
 Exploratory Data Analysis(EDA) Data Visualization    Develop solutions
 Establish a baseline Machine Learning Models Hyperparameter Tuning &amp;amp; Optimization Best model    Defining The Problem Can we predict the right loan applicant from their background?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Boot Camp</title>
      <link>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/certs/cert_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/certs/cert_5/</guid>
      <description>  What did I learn through this course?  Programming with Python NumPy with Python Using pandas Data Frames to solve complex tasks Use pandas to handle Excel Files Web scraping with python Connect Python to SQL Use matplotlib and seaborn for data visualizations Use plotly for interactive visualizations Machine Learning with SciKit Learn, including: Linear Regression K Nearest Neighbors K Means Clustering Decision Trees Random Forests Natural Language Processing Neural Nets and Deep Learning Support Vector Machines  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salary Predictions</title>
      <link>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>github url
Salary Prediction Objective: Can we predict the right salary for the given job
Table of contents   Define Problem
 Can we predict the right salary for the job description? Goals    Discover Data
 Exploratory Data Analysis(EDA) Data Visualization    Develop solutions
 Establish a baseline Machine Learning Models Hyperparameter Tuning &amp;amp; Optimization Best model    Deploy solution
 Automate the pipeline Save the predictions    Defining The Problem Can we predict the right salary for the job description?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coursera Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/certs/cert_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 09:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/certs/cert_3/</guid>
      <description>  certificate
What is this course? This course has provided me a broad introduction to
 machine learning datamining statistical pattern recognition.  Topics include:
 (i) Supervised learning (parametric/non-parametric algorithms, support vector machines, kernels, neural networks). (ii) Unsupervised learning (clustering, dimensionality reduction, recommender systems, deep learning). (iii) Best practices in machine learning (bias/variance theory; innovation process in machine learning and AI).  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sa616473.github.io/Tj_portfolio_1/contact/</guid>
      <description>This is an example of a custom shortcode that you can put right into your content. You will need to add a form action to the the shortcode to make it work. Check out Formspree for a simple, free form service.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>